I'm diagnosed with pituitary adenoma at
36 years old I had it before puberty
should I start with HCG and cber first
or do cber HCG and CP unate or cream I'm
also obese just your opinion on it
please so generally pituitary adomas
will lead to hyper
prolactinoma and it will lead to hypo
gluing hormone which means that you're
not secreting sufficient gatot tropic s
to stimulate the LX cells and the
testicles to produce sufficient levels
of testosterone and if that's the case
and that is why you're hypogonadal first
and foremost I imagine this was
diagnosed via MRI and if it is in fact
benign and I presume that it is since it
was brought on as such a young age they
will continue to monitor that adenoma
for any potential growth or malignancies
in the future but in the meantime uh if
you're a candidate for trt depending on
what country you live in I suggest you
get with a provider who is very
proficient um and can manage you
correctly I mean they should know at
least at the very Basics the same stuff
that I know and uh if they understand
that then they should be able to manage
it correctly as far as the mode of
administration again that is up to you
and your provider once they've given you
full uh information on you know pros and
cons of each method